equal: v.   等于
Lesson 2.13 equals 1.
第2.13课等于1。
Our Vickr is always raising money for one cause or another.
我们的Vickr总是为一个或另一个原因筹集资金。
But he has never managed to get enough money to have the church clock repaired.
但是他从来没有设法获得足够的钱来维修教堂的时钟。
The big clock which used to strike the hours day and night was damaged many years ago and
过去几年和黑夜曾经打动几个小时的大时钟被损坏了，并且
has been.
一直是。
Silent ever since.
从那以后保持沉默。
One night, however, our Vickr work up with a start.
但是，有一天，我们的Vickr开始工作。
The clock was striking the hours.
时钟打动了小时。
Looking at his watch.
看着他的手表。
He saw that it was one o'clock.
他看到那是一点点。
But the bell struck 13 times before it stopped.
但是钟声击中了13次，然后停止了。
Armed with a torch, the Vickr went up into the clock tower to see what was going on.
维克（Vickr）用火炬武装，进入了钟楼，看看发生了什么事。
In the torch light, he caught sight of a figure whom he immediately recognized as Bill Wilkins.
在火炬的灯光中，他看到了一个他立即被认为是比尔·威尔金斯的人物。
Our local grocer.
我们当地的杂货商。
Whatever are you doing up here Bill?
你在这里做什么账单？
Ask the Vickr in surprise.
惊讶地问Vickr。
I'm trying to repair the bell, answered Bill.
比尔回答，我正在试图修理铃铛。
I've been coming up here night after night for weeks now.
我一直在夜晚夜间来这里数周。
You see, I was hoping to give you a surprise.
你看，我希望给你一个惊喜。
You certainly did give me a surprise.
你当然给我一个惊喜。
Said the Vickr, you've probably woken up everyone in the village as well.
Vickr说，您也可能也把村里的每个人都醒了。
Still, I'm glad the bell is working again.
不过，我很高兴铃铛再次工作。
That's the trouble.
那是麻烦。
Vickr, answered Bill.
Vickr，回答比尔。
It's working all right.
一切正常。
But I'm afraid that at one o'clock it will strike 13 times and there's nothing I can
但是我恐怕一点点会击中13次，而我无能为力
do about.
做。
It will get used to that.
它将习惯。
Bill said the Vickr.
比尔说Vickr。
13 is not as good as one.
13不如一个。
But it's better than nothing.
但总比没有好。
Now let's go downstairs and have a cup of tea.
现在让我们下楼，喝杯茶。